

+212693399476

Aminemazza6@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/amine-mazza

🙎 Marrakech, Maroc

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE

· Front-end:

Html - Css - Bootstrap TailwindCss - JavaScript Angular - React Js

• Back-end: Java - PHP - C++

Frameworks: Spring-Laravel-Symfony

API : APIplatform-REST-SOAP

Databases:MySQL - Oracle

Design:UML - Merise

Project Management:
 Agile methodology: Scrum
 Trello - ClickUp
 Git - GiHub - GitLab

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Discipline
- Initiative
- Teamwork

LANGUAGES

- Arabic
- French
- English

CENTRES OF INTEREST

- Photography
- Chess
- Reading

Amine MAZZA

Engineering student in Computer Science and Information Systems

As a student in the final year of computer engineering and information systems, I have a strong passion for computer science and have gained practical experience in the design and implementation of web applications.

EDUCATION:

- **ENGINEERING CYCLE:** Informatics and Information Systems Location: Private University of Marrakech 2022-2024
- BACHELOR DEGREE: Technologies and Web Programming Location: Faculty of Sciences Semlalia 2021-2022
- BAC: Science of Physics
 Location: Lycée Abou Elabbas Essabti 2017-2018

EXPERIENCES:



PFA - internship (May 2023 - July 2023)

 Subject: the contribution to the development of a web application that will allow a travel agency to manage all its operations in an efficient and automated way, including a newsletter system.



PFE - internship (May 2022 - June 2022)

 Subject: the design and development of a web application to connect customers with handymen, and to facilitate the work of the administrator to manage handymen and Services.

ACADEMIC PROJECTS:

- The design and development of an innovative web and mobile platform for online ordering of healthy meals for customers looking for nutritious dishes adapted to their diet.
 - Repo: https://github.com/AmineMazza/Koul-Healthy
- The design and implementation of a platform collects, processes and analyzes data from potential restaurant customers to provide location recommendations to existing or planned restaurants.
 - Repo: https://github.com/AmineMazza/Dish-Discover